LEUNG Sin Tung, Hazel

Contact number: +852 9638 9412 Email: leungsintunghazel@gmail.com

Profile

As a passionate and dynamic Accounting & Finance graduate student, I am able to equip myself with strong problem-solving skills and team-building competence along with pro-active attitude and clear, logical mind. Holding a genuine interest in accounting, my strengths in analytical and presentation skills are essential in commercial finance. A wide range of work experience also shows my adaptability to face the ever-changing financial market.

Education & Qualifications

2014-2017 Lancaster University Management School

BSc (Hons) Accounting & Finance Degree Upper Second

In Top 3 UK Business Schools, Modules: Economics, Financial and Managerial Accounting, Accounting Information Systems, Finance, Investments, Marketing, Project and risk management

2013-2014 EF University Preparation Course

IELTS: 7.5 for overall band score

Average 80% for Mathematics, Accounting and Qualitative and Quantitative study

2007-2013 Cheung Chuk Shan College All:4

DSE subjects: English, Chinese, Mathematics, Liberal Studies, History, Chinese Literature & Business, Accounting and Finance Studies

Working Experience

2017 September-December Account Assistant, Langham Hall

- -Responsible for providing accounting services for private equity clients, support the preparation of financial statements with the analysis of financial information
- -Recording transactions including bookkeeping, bank reconciliations, fair value adjustments
- -Deal with third parties such as auditors for external advices and liaison with client's working team to request accounting information and discuss any issue

2015; 2017 June-September Summer Internship (Branded Products), Maxim's Caterers Ltd

- -Multi-tasking assistant to Branded Products Department handling of full set of trading documents and data entry, using Tradelink software to accomplish the declaration form, Microsoft Word and Excel to complete filing procedures
- -The preparation of contract, invoice, packing list and CEPA forms requiring high accuracy and quality of work while meeting deadlines under pressure

2014-2017 September-June Lancaster University Students Unions Retail Assistant, LUSU

- -To adhere and uphold shop operational procedures relating to: till operations, stock control and EPOS Systems, merchandising and promotion as well as customer service
- -Contribute to improvement of shop's service by attending shop meetings with effectively communicate any operational issues to managers
- -Develop my flexibility to work under pressure, being reliable and responsible and pay attention to details

2012 January-February Entrepreneur, Lunar New Year Stall Operation at Victoria Park

- Negotiate with wholesalers and persuade potential customers to purchase
- Allocate duties according to staff abilities which has strengthened my interpersonal skills
- Produce financial statements to help deliver strategic and innovative advice on marketing

Further Skills

◆ Language & Speech

2016 Lancaster Award: Gold

- -The Lancaster award is developed in partnership with UK employers, which is a certificate that rewards students who engages in a wide range of activities to acquire skills that valued by employers.
- -For the Gold Level, students are requested to achieve 65+ points in different categories: work experience, campus activities, career workshops and volunteering.

2012 Certificate of Completion & Outstanding performance

-Final Level of Kumon Mathematics Program: illustrates the well-developed statistical analysis

2011 Certificate of Merit, Speech Festival English Solo Verse Speaking

Award for Outstanding Cooperation, HK School Drama Festival

-Confident to deliver various public speeches and strong verbal communication

◆ Leadership & Community Services

2014-2017 Event Executive, Lancaster University Investment and Finance society

- Organise different networking opportunities for students who are interested in pursuing their career in financial sector
- -In past, we have invited PwC for giving a workshop related to interview skills and assessment center; City Careers is our largest event which Management school alumni are invited to share their experience in financial industry. For example, we have current hedge fund manager from UBS to give support to our members. Also, we usually held networking events: LUMS societies networking collaboration.

2014-2017 Department leader, Chinese Students and Scholars' Association

- Specialized in External Affairs Department
- Persuaded local business such as Chinese supermarket and restaurants to offer student discount
- Raised funds for New Year Show by advertising sponsors' shops in campus
- Organized department committee meetings
- Promoted the association using variety of media, Facebook page, WeChat and website etc.

2014 Drama Director of Variety Show, Lancaster University Hong Kong Society

- -Produced a play with around 90 minutes, have further strengthened my interpersonal and communication skills as well as the leadership ability to gather the cohesion.
- -Willing to take responsibility to coordinate with the other team in the show, likes Dance crew

2012 *Treasurer*, Junior Police Call Club

- Good practice to keep a petty cash book and merge with the statement of profits and loss
- Ensure the annual report is error-free and the records can be tracked with relevant entry provided

◆ *Volunteers*

2014-2017 Oxfam Volunteer shop assistant, Lancaster

- Multi-tasking duties are required such as setting an affordable price for items, keeping the shop tidy, and handling requests from customers

2011 Bronze Award for Volunteer Service, Social Welfare Department

Committee, Cheung Chuk Shan College Volunteer Team Volunteer, U-Hearts Teenage Exchange Programme Student Ambassador, Parent's Day

◆ Music & Oversea Studies

2012 July Participant, National Education Exchange Program in Mainland for Secondary students

-English teaching volunteers: enables me to break the language barriers, strengthens my communication skills as well as develop my interpersonal skills

2012 April Participant, Passing on the Torch: National Education Exchange Program in Shanghai

2011 July Exchange Student, EF International Language Center in Oxford

-First time of overseas study: foster my adaptability to immerse in local customs, being independent, self-motivated and in addition to emotional intelligence to take care myself

2010 Pass, ABRSM Grade 7 violin

Most Outstanding Member Award, the Island Youth Strings